The Macabre is a horror film directed by Eric Mathis.
Shy girl Molly is having a party.
She is inviting her school bullies and has planned one hell of a night.
After a party trick goes horribly wrong, each guest is forced into a macabre game of life
and death by an ancient demon who forces them to tell horrifying stories.
Wendy, played by Corinna Harney.
Ms. Lady Sinister, played by Maritza Brikisak.
Mr. Macabre, played by John Dugan.
Vicki, played by Lindsey Cruz.
Johnny Rightman, played by Aaron Groben.
Molly, played by Arianna Lexus.
In art, the term macabre (US:  or UK: ; French: [makabʁ]) means "having
the quality of having a grim or ghastly atmosphere".
The macabre emphasises the details and symbols of death.
The tone is dark.